Guide to the Intercollegiate Center for Nursing Education Director (Hilda Boerhave Roberts) Papers 1924-2001
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Courses, Series 6
  - Nursing 598: Special Topics - Spring 1988 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 598: Special Topics - Fall 1988 to Spring 1989 (Folder 9)
  - Nursing 598: Special Topics - Fall 1989 to Spring 1990 (Folder 10)
  - Nursing 598: Special Topics - Fall 1990 to Spring 1991 (Folder 11)
  - Nursing 598: Special Topics - Spring 1992 (Folder 12)
  - Nursing 598: Special Topics - Fall 1992 (Folder 13)
  - Nursing 598: Special Topics - Fall 1994 (Folder 14)
  - Nursing 598: Special Topics - Spring 1996 (Folder 15)
  - Nursing Course: Basic Course in Nursing Tuberculosis - 1951 to 1954 (Folder 16)
  - Nursing Course Textbook Lists and Correspondence - 1953 to 1980 (Folder 17)
  - Nursing Education 01: History of Nursing - 1946 to 1950 (Folder 18)
  - Nursing Education 01: History of Nursing, Hilda B. Roberts Notes - 1940s to 1950s (Folder 19)
  - Nursing Education 41: Methods of Teaching in Nursing Education - 1947 to 1952 (Folder 20)
  - Nursing Education 95: Professional Adjustments II - 1940s (Folder 21)
  - Nursing Education 96c: Introduction to Public Health - 1949 (Folder 22)
  - Nursing Education 97c: Public Health Field Work - 1947 to 1950 (Folder 23)
  - Nursing Education 152c: Ward Management Course Materials and Hilda B. Roberts Lecture Notes - 1940 to 1950 (Folder 24)
  - Nursing Education 192e: Pre-Clinical Achievement Exam - Spring 1946 (Box 162, Folder 1)
  - Nursing Education 335: Methods of Teaching in Nursing Education - Fall 1953 to Spring 1954 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing Education 456c - Fall 1952 to Spring 1953 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing Independent Study - 1975 to 1976 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing Skills Lab- Fall 1974 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing Skills Lab- Spring 1975 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing Supportive Courses - Fall 1975 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing Supportive Courses - Winter 1975-1976 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing Supportive Courses - Spring 1976 (Folder 9)
  - Pharmacy 360: Essentials of Pharmacology - 1970 (Folder 10)
  - Pharmacy 360: Essentials of Pharmacology - Summer 1971 (Folder 11)
  - Pharmacy 360: Essentials of Pharmacology - Summer 1972 (Folder 12)
  - Pharmacy 360: Essentials of Pharmacology - Summer 1973 (1 of 2) (Box 163, Folder 1)
  - Pharmacy 360: Essentials of Pharmacology - Summer 1973 (2 of 2) (Folder 2)
  - Pharmacy 360: Essentials of Pharmacology - Fall 1975 (Folder 3)
  - Pharmacy 417: Non-Prescription Analgesics - Fall 1976 (Folder 4)
  - Psychology 210: Developmental Psychology - Fall 1971 to Spring 1972 (Folder 5)
  - Psychology 210: Developmental Psychology - Fall 1972 to Spring 1973 (Folder 6)
  - Psychology 240: Developmental Psychology - Spring 1974 (Folder 7)
  - Psychology 311: Statistics - Spring 1975 (Folder 8)
  - Psychology 333/357/359/461: Deviant Behavior/Abnormal Psychology - Spring 1974 (Folder 9)
  - Psychology 333/357/359/461: Deviant Behavior/Abnormal Psychology - Winter 1974-1975 (Folder 10)
  - Social Stratification - Fall 1973 (Folder 11)
  - Sociology 356: Introduction to Social Research - Spring 1974 (Folder 12)
  - Sociology 356: Introduction to Social Research - Fall 1974 (Folder 13)
  - Sociology 421: Criminology - Fall 1974 (Folder 14)
  - Zoology 10: Elementary Human Anatomy - 1943 to 1945 (Folder 15)
  - Zoology 10: Human Anatomy for Nurses - 1049 to 1950 (Folder 16)